[
    {
        "question":"What do you mean by triage system?",
        "options":[
            "Prioritization of patients needing immediate care",
            "Prioritization of patients into those requiring treatment and those who don't",
            "Prioritization of all patients into those requiring immediate treatment",
            "Prioritization of all patients needing immediate care"
        ],
        "answer":"Prioritization of all patients into those requiring immediate treatment"
    },
    {
        "question":"What scenario originally identified the need of a triage process.",
        "options":[
            "Road accident",
            "War",
            "Volcanic Eruption",
            "EarthQuake"
        ],
        "answer":"War"
    },
    {
        "question":"One triage method is START. What does START stand for? ",
        "options":[
            "Simple Triage and Rapid Treatment",
            "Start Taking and Rapid Tracking",
            "Simple Tasking and Rapid Termination",
            "Start Talking and Reassess Treatment"
        ],
        "answer":"Simple Triage and Rapid Treatment"
    },
    {
        "question":"What are the color codes for triage system?",
        "options":[
            "Black, pink, yellow, green",
            "Black, red, pink, green",
            "Black, red, yellow, green",
            "Black, pink, blue, yellow"
        ],
        "answer":"Black, red, yellow, green"
    },
    {
        "question":"Black represents",
        "options":[
            "Severely ill",
            "Dead",
            "Not sure",
            "No need for care"
        ],
        "answer":"Dead"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which color code would be given the highest priority.",
        "options":[
            "Blue",
            "Pink",
            "Red",
            "Black"
        ],
        "answer":"Red"
    },
    {
        "question":"If a patient has only scars seen in the limbs, what triage would be tagged?",
        "options":[
            "Green",
            "Yellow",
            "Blue",
            "Pink"
        ],
        "answer":"Green"
    },
    {
        "question":"How many stages are present in a triage system?",
        "options":[
            "5",
            "4",
            "2",
            "3"
        ],
        "answer":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"These are the roles of a triage nurse except",
        "options":[
            "To completely assess all the incoming patients",
            "Avoid maintain public moral",
            "To properly place the in categories",
            "Utilization of available resources"
        ],
        "answer":"Avoid maintain public moral"
    },
    {
        "question":"Triage which victim first?",
        "options":[
            "The worst looking victim",
            "The worst sounding victim",
            "The closest victim",
            "The youngest victim"
        ],
        "answer":"The closest victim"
    },
    {
        "question":"A victim appears quite still when you get to them. You shake the victim and shout. They do not respond. What do you do next?",
        "options":[
            "Go to the next person",
            "Open the airway",
            "Shout again",
            "Tag them red"
        ],
        "answer":"Open the airway"
    },
    {
        "question":"A victim is moaning. What do you do next?",
        "options":[
            "Check their capillary refill",
            "Count respiration for 15 secs",
            "Open the airway",
            "Ask them why they are moaning"
        ],
        "answer":"Check their capillary refill"
    },
    {
        "question":"The pitfalls of triage include",
        "options":[
            "Inadequate medical size-up",
            "No team plan, organization or goal",
            "Indecisive leadership",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer":"All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question":"A fire broke out in a particular locality. One of the wounded is able to walk around and has minor lacerations in the arms, hands, chest and legs. What color tag would be placed on the survivor?",
        "options":[
            "Red",
            "Yellow",
            "Green",
            "Black"
        ],
        "answer":"Green"
    },
    {
        "question":"The wounded victim is unable to walk, respiratory rate is absent but when airway is repositioned breathing is noted. The wounded victim is assigned what tag Color?",
        "options":[
            "Green",
            "Red",
            "Yellow",
            "Black"
        ],
        "answer":"Red"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which statement below is INCORRECT about the yellow triage tag color in regards to a disaster situation?",
        "options":[
            "These victims are seen after patients with the green tag color",
            "Can have treatment delayed for an hour or less",
            "These victims has serious injuries which can be life threatening if treatment is delayed",
            "A survivor with this tag color has second priority for treatment of injuries"
        ],
        "answer":"These victims are seen after patients with the green tag color"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which do you not do during triage?",
        "options":[
            "CPR",
            "Cool a burn",
            "Treat hypothermia",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer":"All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question":"All victims who cannot walk are considered ‘immediate’",
        "options":[
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer":"False"
    },
    {
        "question":"As per the principles, the tagged victim should be cared with--\nRed – see immediately.\nYellow – see within ____ mins.\nGreen – see within ____ mins.",
        "options":[
            "60 & 120 mins respectively",
            "120 & 240 mins respectively",
            "30 & 60 mins respectively",
            "Both A & B"
        ],
        "answer":"60 & 120 mins respectively"
    },
    {
        "question":"To reduce anxiety of a victim you can",
        "options":[
            "Talk with them as you do a head-to-toe assessment",
            "Pay careful attention to what they say to you",
            "Give a false assurance of arrival of ambulance",
            "A & B"
        ],
        "answer":"A & B"
    }

]
